"May I have a slice of watermelon?" asks the old woman.
你可以给我一块西瓜吗 老妇人说
"Yes, here you are," says Helen.
可以 给你 海伦说
"You are a very kind girl," says the old woman.
你是一个善良的女孩 老妇人说
She takes a feather out of her pocket.
她从口袋里拿出一片羽毛
Take this feather. Make a wish. Then blow hard.
拿着羽毛 许一个愿望 然后用劲吹
Your wish will come true.' says the old woman.
你的愿望会实现 老妇人说
"Thank you," says Helen.
谢谢你 海伦说
"Oh! Where is she?" says Helen.
噢 她去哪里了 海伦说
Helen goes home after school.
海伦放学回家
"I haven't got any food for dinner," says Helen's mother.
我没有任何事物做晚饭了   海伦的妈妈说
Helen takes out the feather.
海伦拿出羽毛
She closes her eyes and makes a wish.
她闭上眼睛并许愿
Helen blows very hard.
海伦用劲吹
"It's raining!"shouts Helen's mother.
下雨了 海伦的妈妈大声叫道
"Rain! Rain!" shouts Helen's mother.
雨 雨 海伦的妈妈大声叫道
"What a lot of fish!" shouts Helen.
有好多鱼 海伦大声叫道
Helen's mother cooks a large meal for all the people in her village.
海伦的妈妈给全村的人做了一大桌美食
They are all very happy.
他们都很开心